Tang Wei Xun +65 8768 3698 w31.xun.tang@gmail.com Singapore Citizen

## **SUMMARY**

IT Professional with 4+ years of experience in development web, batch and solution for diverse industry clients. Highly instrumental in all phases of the SDLC. Keen on continuous learning to take on exciting challenges. Passionate with development to built solution out of ideas.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Sr. System Application Support

07/2023 - Present

#### Visa Worldwide

- Led automation initiatives to enhance team efficiency and streamline operations.
- Revamped a Spring Boot project for JAX-RS, improving application performance and functionality.
- Developed and implemented a Python script for compliance reporting, ensuring regulatory adherence and enhancing data accuracy.

## Visa Worldwide

- Tasked with gaining competency in Shell scripting and Power Shell scripting.
- Attended professional diploma courses in Software Development at NUS.
- Developed a web-based bus/route application as mini projects to inform users about upcoming timing arrivals and provide instructions for reaching their destinations.

## Singapore Airlines

# **Full Stack Developer (Apprenticeship)**

07/2021 - 12/2021

- Created and assisted with the development of the <u>Flight Schedule</u> and <u>Express Booking</u> office website using JavaScript, Java, React, CSS.
- Had the opportunity to work on VTL changes.
- Debugged and implemented stipulation given by product owner.
- Leveraged on git bucket for version control and attended scrum ceremonies daily to ensure project delivery in the allocated time.

## **Software Engineer Associate**

07/2018 - 10/2020

### Accenture

- Applied technical expertise to build, test and deploy based on specification issued by functional team.
- Designed, developed, troubleshot, debugged, tested, ensured browser compatibility, implemented website code by using Java, Spring MVC and mayen.
- Unit test methods utilizing Java to ensure quality of functionality.
- Conducted investigation on issues raised by users and implemented resolutions.
- Worked closely with Team Leads on change request functions.

## **Software Engineer New Associate**

08/2016 - 06/2018

#### Accenture

- Showcased new software changes to product owners.
- Conducted investigation on issues raised by users and implement resolutions.
- Developed applications utilizing maven in Java (Spring & Hibernate) project.
- Utilized docu-sign API to digitally sign documents programmatically.

### **Android Developer (Internship)**

04/2016 - 08/2015

### ST Electronics

- Collaborated with ST Electronics for requirements & translated into specifications for the development team.
- Collaborated with supervisor for new initiatives & in charge of the overall technical solutioning.

• Identified areas to improve in terms of productivity, propose, design solution, prototype & implement.

EDUCATION	
National University Of Singapore	05/2022 - 05/2023
Singapore	
<ul> <li>Professional Diploma In Software Development</li> </ul>	
Temasek Polytechnic	07/2021 – 12/2021
Singapore	
<ul> <li>Industry Attachment (SGUP-CT – Microsoft Junior Full-Stack Developer)</li> </ul>	
Temasek Polytechnic	03/2021 – 06/2021
Singapore	
<ul> <li>Junior Full Stack Developer Bootcamp</li> </ul>	
Temasek Polytechnic	01/2016 - 01/2017
Singapore	
<ul> <li>Specialist Diploma in Smart Solution</li> </ul>	
Temasek Polytechnic	01/2014 - 01/2016
Singapore	
<ul> <li>Diploma in Info-Comm Network Engineering</li> </ul>	
Institute of Technical Education	01/2009 - 01/2010
Singapore	
<ul> <li>Nitec in Info-Comm Network Engineering</li> </ul>	

## **COMPUTER SKILLS**

## Languages

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Thymeleaf, BootStrap, Angular15,
- Java (Spring, Maven, Hibernate)

# **Software**

- Database: Oracle MySQL, MongoDB
- Repository: Git
- Platforms: Microsoft Windows 10, Linux Lubuntu

### LINKS

GITHUB: <a href="https://github.com/weixuntang">https://github.com/weixuntang</a>

LINKEDIN: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tang-wei-xun-8b4044136/